myyearbook.com 2011-04-29

# myYearbook | Privacy

Last Updated September 24, 2010  

* * *

myYearbook.com takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. Also note that your use of myYeabook.com, along with disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use. myYearbook.com shall comply with all applicable laws. 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how myYearbook.com treats information that myYearbook.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of myYearbook.com products and services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that myYearbook.com does not own or control (including, but not limited to, advertisers), or to people that myYearbook.com does not employ or pay. 

**Information Collection and Use**

myYearbook.com collects information when you register with myYearbook.com, when you use myYearbook.com products or services, and when you visit myYearbook.com pages or the pages of certain myYearbook.com affiliates, vendors, or advertisers. myYearbook.com may collect information about you and your use of the website that is both personal and non-personal. For purposes of this policy, "personal information" is information about you that can be used to personally identify you, such as your email address, and that is not otherwise publicly available. "Non-personal" information is everything else. 

When you register to use myYearbook.com we ask for information such as your email address, birth date, gender, etc. Once you register with myYearbook.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

myYearbook.com may also collect information about your transactions with us and your transactions with our business affiliates, vendors, and advertisers, including information about your use of products offered through the website. myYearbook.com may also collect information about you from other sources, such as blogs and instant messaging services, and other users of myYearbook.com services. myYearbook.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, myYearbook.com cookie information (including without limitation cookies, flash cookies, and beacons), and the pages you request. myYearbook.com may use some or all of your information for the following general purposes: 

  * To customize your experience 
  * To customize advertising and content you see 
  * To fulfill your requests for products and services 
  * To offer customized features 
  * To improve our services 
  * To contact you 
  * To conduct research 

These activities, in part, help to underwrite the cost of the content and services made available to you online. Note that, in general, tracking of a user's online activities over time -- including the searches conducted, the web pages visited, and the content viewed -- in order to deliver targeted advertising is considered online behavioral advertising. NOTE THAT MYYEARBOOK USERS ARE SUBJECT TO ONLINE BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING AND/OR MULTI-SITE ADVERTISING. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

myYearbook.com may share with or sell to affiliates, vendors, advertisers, and other non-related third parties your non-personal information for commercial purposes. myYearbook.com may also share with affiliates, vendors, advertisers, and other non-related third parties your non-personal information in order to allow myYearbook.com and its affiliates, vendors, advertisers and other non-related third parties to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience. However, myYearbook.com does not sell, rent or otherwise provide your personal information to any third parties without your permission, other than as specified below: 

  * myYearbook.com may share your personal and/or non-personal information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes, or, when necessary, to establish or exercise myYearbook.com's legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
  * myYearbook.com may share your personal and/or non-personal information with appropriate authorities when myYearbook.com, in its sole discretion, believes that it is necessary to share such information in order to facilitate an investigation, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or in similar situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations or suspected violations of myYearbook.com's terms of use related to personal safety, or as otherwise required by law. 

Notwithstanding any of the aforementioned, be aware that posting personal information on public areas of myYearbook.com (via Profile, Forums, Blogs, etc.) will make your information publicly available. Do not post information in public areas that you want to keep private. Also, be aware that certain information you post or share with third parties like your friends or members of your network about yourself may be shared with other users and all such sharing of information is done at your own risk. 

**Links**

myYearbook.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites that may be linked to myYearbook.com pages. You are solely responsible for reviewing third party privacy policy terms. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by myYearbook.com. 

**Cookies**

myYearbook.com may set and access myYearbook.com cookies on your computer to, among other things, customize the user experience. These files help more precisely target advertising to you based on your activity, but such files do not access or use information by which you can be personally identified. You may realize certain losses of functionality if you turn your cookies off in your browser, or otherwise disable them. 

Affiliates, vendors, advertisers, and other non-related third parties displayed on myYearbook.com may also contain cookies or tag your computer with cookies. myYearbook.com does not control these third party cookies and, for your own benefit, you should check the privacy policy of such third parties. Third party ads displayed on myYearbook.com may also include tags enabling such third parties to collect information about the user's interaction with such ads. For instance, by way of illustration and not limitation, such third party tags may record the date, time, user's geographical location based on the user's IP address, as well as the website to which the ad was delivered, the operating system which the browser was using, and so on. Note that if you choose to block some or all cookies you may not have access to certain myYearbook.com features and you may adversely affect your experience of myYearbook.com's website. 

For more information about cookies, web beacons, and related tools that may be used by myYearbook.com and non-related third parties, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>. 

**Opting Out of Receiving Cookies**

Some of myYearbook's vendors and affiliates are members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI") and as members they comply with NAI's Self-Regulatory Principles which are designed to inform consumers about data collection and advertising practices across multiple web sites and provide the ability to users to opt out. 

YOU MAY OPT OUT OF RECEIVING COOKIES BY CLICKING HERE: [HTTP://NETWORKADVERTISING.ORG/MANAGING/OPT_OUT.ASP](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Note that if you use multiple computers or multiple browsers, you will need to opt out of receiving cookies on each computer and for each browser. Also, if you change computers or delete cookies from your computer you will need to repeat this opt-out process. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

myYearbook.com reserves the right to update and change this Privacy Policy and/or its Terms of Use at any time. All updates and changes to this Privacy Policy and/or its Terms of Use shall take effect immediately. Although myYearbook.com shall announce significant changes by posting a notice prominently on the website for your convenience, you assume the responsibility of periodically reviewing this Privacy Policy and myYearbook.com encourages you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand the current Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, the most current Privacy Policy applies. 

**Physical Address:**  
myYearbook.com  
280 Union Square Drive  
New Hope, PA 18938
